AMIRA IZEDINE

9712 East 116th Street Fishers Indiana 46037 Cell: 260-444-1561 - izedineamira@gmail.com

Summary

Volunteered as a patient safety assistant at my local hospital and gained beneficial experience. Completed many coursework regarding health care and in the process of finishing a degree in Health Services Management from Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis. Enthusiastic and dedicated to gain more experience in the health care industry and interact with patients.

Skills

- Patient and family focused
- Mobility assistance
- Enthusiastic caregiver
- Patient-oriented
- Medical terminology knowledge

Experience

Purchasing Associate

April 2018 to Current

Telamon Corporation — Carmel, IN

- Responsible for issuing purchase orders to suppliers and following up for ship dates and tracking numbers.
- Work closely with many departments including Accounts Payable, Warehouse and
- Quality teams and maintains constant contact with suppliers to ensure timely delivery of products.
- Manage Purchase Orders, dates and tracking with assigned suppliers.
- Utilize ERP to review and provide invoice issue resolution.
- Work with suppliers for on time delivery performance.
- Support sales and engineering quoting requirements for new business opportunities.
- Set up new suppliers in Oracle.
- Pull standard reports and send to Planner and/or supplier.
- Interacted with suppliers and employees at all levels within the organization.
- Produce routine reports and correspondence.
- Solved practical problems and deal with a variety of concrete variables in situations where only limited standardization exists.

Secretary/Coordinator/English Tutor/Volunteer

May 2007 to May 2016

SUDANESE-CHADIAN COMMUNITY — FORT WAYNE, IN

Implemented development programs for the organization.

- Filed basic secretarial and office work.
- Translated documents into English for community members.
- Assisted refugees in settlement programs and obtaining legal documents.
- Helped with job search, transportation, and shelter.
- Conduct classes, workshops, and demonstrations to teach basic English language ADDITIONAL skills.
- WORK Observe and evaluate students' work to determine progress and make suggestions for improvement.
- EXPERIENCE Participate in publicity planning, and community awareness efforts.
- Select and schedule class times to ensure maximum attendance.

Amazon Associate

November 2014 to February 2016

INTEGRITY STAFFING — IN

- Select, and help locate or obtain merchandise based on customer needs and desires.
- Answer questions regarding the warehouse and its merchandise.
- Pick and pack merchandise for shipment.
- Trained perspective employees.

Sales Associate

December 2011 to May 2012

JCPENNY — INDIANAPOLIS, IN

- Provide customer service by greeting and assisting customers and responding to customer inquiries and complaints.
- Examine merchandise to ensure that it is correctly priced and displayed.
- Process merchandise returns and exchanges.
- Stock shelves, and mark prices on shelves and items.

October 2009 to May 2011

PARK VIEW HOSPITAL, ICU — FORT WAYNE, IN

- Answer patient call signals, signal lights, bells, or intercom systems to determine patients' needs.
- Communicate with patients to ascertain feelings or need for assistance or social and emotional support.
- Remind patients to take medications or nutritional supplements.
- Provide information such as directions, visiting hours, or patient status information to visitors or callers.
- Entertain, converse with, or read aloud to patients to keep them mentally healthy and alert.
- Supervised frequent activities such as medication and personal hygiene to ensure safety.
- Monitored clients' progress to report necessary changes.
- Maintained a clean and well-organized environment to promote client happiness and safety.

• Worked to improve patient outlook and daily living through compassionate care.

Education and Training

B.S: Health Services Management, 2019

Indiana University - Purdue University Indianapolis — Indianapolis, IN

Bachelor of Science: General Studies, Math and Science, Dec 2016INDIANA UNIVERSITY

PURDUE UNIVERSITY — INDIANAPOLIS, IN

High School Diploma: May 2008NORTH SIDE HIGH SCHOOL — FORT WAYNE, IN

Activities and Honors

Chase Leadership Academy Award IRS Certified Tax Preparer volunteered for 3 years at John Boner Community Center-Indianapolis